Guide to the William T. Miller papers, 1941-1992.
Miller, William T. papers
- Alpha Files - Cornell M-Z and Chemistry Department Newsletters
  - New York Academy of Sciences, Undated (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - W.A. Noyes Jr., Editor J.A.C.S., Undated (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Fluorocarbon Nomenclature, Undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - News Clippings, F-Chem., Undated (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - M.L. Nichols, Undated (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Malden C. Nesheim, Undated (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - N's, Undated (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - O's, Undated (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Organic Chemistry @ Cornell, Early History from Rhodes MS, Undated (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Linus Pauling, Undated (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - R.A. Plaine, Undated (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Earl Peters, Undated (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Prize Winners & Prizes, Undated (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - James A. Perkins, Pres. Of Cornell, Undated (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - P's, Undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Paul R. Resnick, Undated (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Frank H.T. Rhodes, Pres. Of Cornell Univ., Undated (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Electrolytic Fluorination, Undated (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - R,s, Undated (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Hunter R. Rawlings III, Undated (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - S's, Undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - H.A. Schevaga, Undated (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Dotservi Y. Sogah, Undated (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Carol A. Sperati, Undated (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Phil Skell, Undated (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Mike Sienko, Undated (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Kirby V. Scherer, Jr., Undated (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Jean' ne M. Shreeve, Undated (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Robert L. Soulen, Undated (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - D.W.A. Sharp, Glasgow Univ. Prof., Undated (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - AI Thonpson, Undated (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Truth ?, Undated (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - J.C. Tallow, Undated (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - T's, Undated (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Paul Tarrant, Undated (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - U's, Undated (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - V's, Undated (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Winstein, S., Undated (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Cheves Walling- Ed. VACS, Undated (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Welch Foundation, Undated (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - R.B. Woodward, Undated (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Ben Widom, Chairman Chem. Dept., Undated (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - George Wyman, Undated (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - John R. Wiesenf eld, Undated (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - W's, Undated (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Field W. Winslow, Undated (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - XYZ's, Undated (Box 7, Folder 63)
  - Chemistry in the Spring at Cornell, Undated (Box 7, Folder 64)
  - Chem. Dept, Rating's- News Items, Undated (Box 7, Folder 65)
  - Dept. Of Chern. News Letters, Undated (Box 7, Folder 66)
  - Chem. Dept News Letters, Undated (Box 7, Folder 67)
  - Chem. Dept. Staff and Student Photos, Undated (Box 7, Folder 68)
- Baker Lecture Correspondence and Cards from International Colleagues
  - American Chemical Society - Historical and Local Sect., Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Baker Lectures Charles R, Cantor, 1992-09-1992-11 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Gabor A. Sommjai, Undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Lipscomb, Wm N., Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - J.M. Lehn, Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Jack D. Duntiz, Undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Charles N. Reilly, 1979-09-1979-11 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - E.L Muetterties, Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Jack Lewis, Undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Michel Szwavc, Undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Katchalski, Ephraim, Undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - H.C. Brown, Undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Dulio Arigoni, Undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - G. Herzberg, Undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - S.l. Weissman, Undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - V.Prolog "Valdo" Vladimir, Undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Professor Edgar Heilbonner, Undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Proposed Baker Lectures, Undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Ralph K. Ilev, Undated (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Housing for Baker Lectures, Undated (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Saul Winstein, Undated (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Pierre Gilles de Gennes, Undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Bill's Book Revised, Undated (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Baker Lecture Kitchen Kit, Undated (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - A.M. Sargeson, Undated (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Voyevodskiy, V.V., Undated (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Baker Laboratory, Undated (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Baker Parties, Undated (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Baker Committee Meetings, Undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Lists of Baker Lectures, Undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Baker Lect., Cornell Press, Undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Baker Lectureship, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - List of Baker Lectures, Undated (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Baker- Hist. Introductions, Undated (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Baker Lecture History, Undated (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Baker Lectureship Letters, Undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - Baker Books - WTM' s, Undated (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - Baker Ratification, Undated (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - Mobay - Bayer Lectures, Miles Lectures, Baker Lectures and Lectures List Of History, Undated (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - J. Burton, Undated (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - Biology Plans, Undated (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Biotech Building Dedication, Undated (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Remodeling Baker Teaching Labratories, Undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - Debye lectureship, Undated (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - New Wing Dedication, Undated (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - O.R. English, Undated (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Departmental Requests for Funds, Undated (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - Fellheimer & Wagner, Correspondence, Undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - History - Cornell Dept., Undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - 300 Seat Lecture Room, Undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Lecture Class Rooms, Undated (Box 8, Folder 51)
  - F.A. Long, Vice president for Research, Undated (Box 8, Folder 52)
  - T.W. Mackesey, Undated (Box 8, Folder 53)
  - Material Science Bldg., Undated (Box 8, Folder 54)
  - Space- WT Miller, Undated (Box 8, Folder 55)
  - WTM's Baker Lab Remodelong, Undated (Box 8, Folder 56)
  - NSF Site Visit to Cornell, Undated (Box 8, Folder 57)
  - News Clippings, Undated (Box 8, Folder 58)
  - New Wing Costs, Undated (Box 8, Folder 59)
  - Special Research Facilities, Undated (Box 8, Folder 60)
  - Research Proposals Reviewed by W.T. Miller, Undated (Box 8, Folder 61)
  - Research Proposals Reviewed by W.T. Miller, Undated (Box 8, Folder 62)
  - W.R. Schlotzhauer, Undated (Box 8, Folder 63)
  - Space, Undated (Box 8, Folder 64)
  - Original Requests for Design Info. For Baker & New Wing, Undated (Box 8, Folder 65)
  - Architect's Representation of New Wing, Program for New Wing, Undated (Box 8, Folder 66)
  - Photo of Artist Rendering of New Wing, Undated (Box 8, Folder 67)
  - Scheraga, Undated (Box 8, Folder 68)
  - Building Programs, Undated (Box 8, Folder 69)
  - Space Program, Undated (Box 8, Folder 70)
  - Teaching Lab Inquires, Undated (Box 8, Folder 71)
  - New Wing, Undated (Box 8, Folder 72)
  - Russian Chemists, Undated (Box 8, Folder 73)
  - Chinese Chemists, Undated (Box 8, Folder 74)
  - Israel, Undated (Box 8, Folder 75)
  - Foreign Chemists, Undated (Box 8, Folder 76)
  - Cards from International Colleagues, Undated (Box 8, Folder 77)
  - Cards from International Colleagues, Undated (Box 8, Folder 78)
- Baker Lab Renovation Files and Reprints, Correspondence with Smithsonian
  - Building Plans and Photos, Undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Building Plans, Undated (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Chem. Dept. History, Undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Chem. Lab. Teaching Program, Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Chemistry Community Courier, Undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - The Alchemist, Undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - RE: Univ. Professorships, Undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Building and Properties, Undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Cranch Committee Report, Undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - University Policy on the Release of Students Records, Undated (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Research Club of Cornell, Undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Faculty Council, Undated (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Building Remodeling Proposal, Undated (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - NSF - Proposal for Laboratory Modification, Undated (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Baker Lab and S.T. Olin Renovation Project, Undated (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - News Bureau, Memos to B.C., Undated (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Baker Program, Program Dir., Red Book, Undated (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Memos to H.A.S., Air Conditioning, Undated (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Application for National Science Foundation Graduate Level Research Facilities Development Grant, Undated (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Program Statement for Space Needs of the Department of Chemistry Cornell University, Undated (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Remodeling Baker Lab, Undated (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Trichloromethyllthium, an Electrophilic Reagent, Undated (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - The Mechanism of Fluorination IV., Undated (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Substitution and Addition reactions of the Fluoroolefins. V. etc., Undated (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Electophilic Reactions of Argentous and Mercuric Fluorides with Fluoroolefins in Hydrogen Fluoride, Undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Cesium Fluoride Catalyzed Rearrangements of Perfluorodienes to Perfluorodialkylacetylenes, Undated (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Substitution and Addn. Rks. IV, Undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Reactions of Alkyllithiums with Polyhalides, Undated (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Substitution and Addition Reactions of the Fluoroolefins. III. Sn2' substitution. Etc., Undated (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Preferential Replacement Reactions of Highly Fluorinated Alkyl Halides. II. Etc., Undated (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Preferential Replacement Reactions of Highly Fluorinated Alkyl Halides. I. Etc., Undated (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Perfluoroalkylzinc Compounds. I. Etc., Undated (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - The Mechanism of Fluorination. III etc., Undated (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - The Mechanism of Fluorination. II, Undated (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - The Mechanism of Fluorination I., Undated (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - The Rearrangement of Chloroflurocarbons by Aluminum Chloride, Undated (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - MDDC- 432- Prep and Reactions, Undated (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - The Thermal Polymerization of Hexafluorobutadiene., Undated (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Vapor Phase Fluorination of Acetyl Fluoide, Undated (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - The Relative Reactivities of Some Substituted Benzyl Fluorides, Undated (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - The Preparation and Properties of some Substituted Benzyl Fluorides, Undated (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - The Addition of methyl Alcohol to Fluoroethylenes, Undated (Box 9, Folder 42)
  - Fluorination of Perhalogen Olefins, Undated (Box 9, Folder 43)
  - Low Polymers of Chlorotrifluoroethylene, Undated (Box 9, Folder 44)
  - Some Complex Sodium Bismuth Salts of Triethanolamine and Triisopropanolamine, Undated (Box 9, Folder 45)
  - Auorochlorethanes as Solvents for the Cryscopic Detn- of Mol. Wts., Undated (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - The Preparation of Unsym.- Difluorotetrachloroethane, Undated (Box 9, Folder 47)
  - The Action of Fluorine Upon some Simple Aliphatic Chlotnated Hydrocarbons, Undated (Box 9, Folder 48)
  - The Vapor Phase Fluorination of Hexachloroethane, Undated (Box 9, Folder 49)
  - A study of the Prep. And Quant. Detr, of Elem., Undated (Box 9, Folder 50)
  - Eli lily Report - Stanford, Undated (Box 9, Folder 51)
  - Smithsonian: Deed of Gift to the Nat. Museum of American History, Undated (Box 9, Folder 52)
  - Jon Eklund, Undated (Box 9, Folder 53)
  - Smithsonian Institution, Undated (Box 9, Folder 54)
  - WTM's Historical Relics, Smithsonian, (CHOC), Undated (Box 9, Folder 55)
  - Public Talks by WTM, Undated (Box 9, Folder 56)
  - Recollections Relating to Fluorine Chemistry, Undated (Box 9, Folder 57)
  - Syn. From F- Octamethylcubane, Undated (Box 9, Folder 58)
  - Synthesis from Perlluoro-2-butyne I. Fluoride Ion Promited Telomerization of Perfluoro-2-butyne, Undated (Box 9, Folder 59)
  - Perfluorophenyl Silver, Undated (Box 9, Folder 60)
  - Perfluoro-1-Methylpropenyl Silver, Undated (Box 9, Folder 61)
  - Perfluoroalkyl Silver, Undated (Box 9, Folder 62)
  - Molar Refractivity in Fluorine - Containing Pethalo Compounds, Undated (Box 9, Folder 63)
  - Re: Smithsonian, Undated (Box 9, Folder 64)
  - WWII Letters re Diffusion plant and WTM's WWII work, Undated (Box 9, Folder 65)
  - Manson Benedict, Undated (Box 9, Folder 66)
  - RE: SAM History - Notes, Undated (Box 9, Folder 67)
  - McLafferty- Compounds for Carbon Clusters, Undated (Box 9, Folder 68)
  - J.L. Heilbron, Undated (Box 9, Folder 69)
  - David Richardson, Undated (Box 9, Folder 70)
  - Miscellaneous, Undated (Box 9)
  - Slides - History of F- Chem. NYC, Undated (Box 9)
  - Slides - Diagmms, Undated (Box 9)
  - Slides - W.T. Miller Apparatus, Undated (Box 9)
  - Pictures, Undated (Box 9)
  - Photographs From General Groves Following WWII research Along With Other Photos, Undated (Box 10)
  - Photographs From Albert F. Thompson, Chief Technical Information Branch, A.E.C 2"d Bomb of the Bikini Test, Undated (Box 10)
  - Photographs Received By W.T. Miller from Maj. Gen. L.R. Groves, Nagasaki, Japan, 1945-08-09 (Box 10)
  - Photographs Received by W.T.Miller from Maj. Gen. L.R. Groves, Hiroshima, Undated (Box 10)
  - Photographs - Trinity Test, Alangardo, New Mexico, Undated (Box 10)
  - Photographs - W.T.Miller, Undated (Box 10)
  - MFP Plasticized with Light MFL 17% 5-20-45, Undated (Box 10)
  - J-Samples 1-5 of MFP-10, Undated (Box 10)
  - Centers form Allis Chamber Pump Shaft Gaskets, Undated (Box 10)
  - MFP Foils include. Blanks to Allis Chambers Pump Shaft Seals, Undated (Box 10)
  - SAM MFP Disc, Undated (Box 10)
  - Test Valve Seats, Undated (Box 10)
  - MFP Carbon Composite Samples, Undated (Box 10)
  - Copolymer Samples, Undated (Box 10)
  - Keel Samples, Undated (Box 10)
  - Round Quenched Disk, Undated (Box 10)
  - SAM Plasticized MFP, Undated (Box 10)
  - Experimental Plastic Trifluorochlorethylene, Undated (Box 10)
  - SAM MFP Samples, Undated (Box 10)
  - MFP Sheets, Undated (Box 10)
  - Small Note Pad Filled with Notes From W.T.Miller, Undated (Box 10)
  - Early SAM Polymer Samples, Undated (Box 10)